



tomvincent95@gmail.com



+491783537914



Paderborn, Germany

SKILLS

C#





Python and Java

















Linux







OpenSSL

















LANGUAGES

Englisch

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

German

Limited Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

Reading

Football

Tom Vincent

Master's student in Paderborn University

Enthusiastic challenge seeker and optimistic problem solver with 3.5 years of software engineering experience. Currently pursuing master's degree in computer science from University of Paderborn by enhancing skills in cyber security, virtual reality, data science and machine learning

Hamburg, Germany

Bangalore, India

Kochi, India

WORK EXPERIENCE

IT SECURITY CONSULTANT (WORK STUDENT) **AON Deutschland**

01/2023 - Present

Achievements/Tasks

Goverence, Risk Analysis and Compliance

ISO 27001 audits

APPLICATION DEVELOPMENT ANALYST

Accenture

05/2017 - 08/2020

Experience

- Selenium Automation
- Quality Assurance
- Application Consultant
- DevOps Engineer

APPLICATION DEVELOPER(INTERN)

Nexgen Solution Providers private Limited

05/2016 - 06/2016

Achievements/Tasks

Worked on enhancing C# application

EDUCATION

Master's in Computer Science UNIVERSITÄT PADERBORN

10/2020 - Present Paderborn, Germany

B.Tech in Computer Science and Engineering KARUNYA UNIVERSITY, INDIA

07/2013 - 05/2017 Coimbatore, India

PROJECTS

Personalized and Collaborative Fitness Training in Virtual Reality (10/2021 - 10/2022)

Created an immersive VR training application with full body tracking and real time feedback in Unity.

Ask and you shall receive: Binary search on anonymous users (04/2021 - 10/2021)

Developed a basic html website to demonstrate how users can be identified without any PII(Personally identifiable information)

Perfolnk (10/2016 - 05/2017)

Developed a stand alone java-based application that collects the academic details of students during various academic years and performs the aggregation and association of data to give a graphical representation of the student's academic progress